advantagz.com 2001-04-09

# Advantagez.com - Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

_**March,** **2000**_

The statement below outlines our privacy policy. This policy is always being updated to reflect our continuing expansion of services and benefits. Our paramount goal is 100% protection of our members' privacy. This policy and the membership agreement are to to be read and acknowledged as one. _ _ __

Any & all information collected will not be given, sold, rented, shared, or traded that will identify personal information regarding our members to any third party, with the exception of third-party contractors who are affiliated with Advantagez.com. Advantagez.com may use or share your information within any of our international subsidiaries only associated with and being part of a transfer of your membership agreement to improve the administration of our services. 

## Legal Disclosure of Your Information

We will surrender personal information to local, state, or federal law enforcement officials if & only the law requires it on an Official legal Documented Request. 

_**_Collection of your Information_** _ __

In our online registration form, we require you to provide us with your full Company name, Contact name, full street address, email address and a password, also a password question with its corresponding answer, so that we may identify you if you ever lose your password. We will process this information to administer your membership.

  ** _ _Our Use of Your Information__** _ _ __

We use your email address to verify your identity and protect against fraud and to contact you. In addition, we use it to send you updates about your account, new products and services, special notifications and company updates. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

Advantagez.com may transfer your personal data internationally to other countries and we will protect your information no matter where we process or store your data by following this privacy statement.

Advantagez.com has centralized its records in the United States. While our head office is in Australia we will be transferring data back and forth to the United States and other countries as they come into operation. 

## Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of your identifiable personal information, such as firewalls, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to Advantagez.com over the Internet the information may travel over many systems that are not under the control of Advantagez.com. The Internet is not 100% secure and others may intercept the information that you are sending.

**Changes to the Policy **

Registering as a member at Advantagez.com, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that our policy may change and certain parts may be amended to assured to absolute privacy of our members, and they will be advised of changes by our advertisement view window. 

**Privacy Questions and Feedback** ** **

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you can contact us _[privacy@advantagez.com ](mailto:privacy@advantagez.com)_

Advantagez.com works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Engage Media manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>

.
